(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-10T13:45:18.732919",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Concert Starting Soon]
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Photosensitivity Warning]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
[Screenshot Policy]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots on SNS are permitted. Screen recordings and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to begin.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
Screenshots may be posted on social media.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
[Penlight Colours Guide]
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the concert to start.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights for production reasons.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS. SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Concert starting soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
[Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights]
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots and uploads to social media are allowed. Audio/video recording, restreaming, and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON DREAMHACK MELBOURNE
Concert Starting Soon - Dreamhack Melbourne
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the concert begins.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
Photosensitivity Warning: Please be aware of flashing lights that may cause discomfort.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS, SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです 録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots and social media uploads are permitted. Recording and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
What is VTuber?
What is a VTuber?
Virtual YouTuber
Stream or create contents
Stream or create content
using 2D and 3D avatar
using 2D and 3D avatars
hololive production has over 70
female and male talents,
active in Japan, Indonesia, and English-speaking countries,
And has over 70 million
YouTube subscribers across all their channels.
We're performing here today!
Have a great time!
Performer Introduction
Ahoy! Captain of the Houshou Pirates!
I am Houshou Marine~!
Konyappi! hololive 4th Gen!
I am Tokoyami Towa!
ZOMBANWA!!!!!!
Super cute zombie idol, kuku- kuku- kuku- Kureiji Ollie!
Super cute zombie idol, kuku-kuku-kuku-Kureiji Ollie!
Attention, please!
I am Pavolia Reine, the Wind Dancing Peacock Maiden!
What's up, Dead Beats!
What's up, Deadbeats!
The Grim Reaper's first apprentice!
WAZZUP!!!
It's everyone's global rat idol Hakos Baelz!
Are you ready?
hololive production x DREAMHACK
DOWN UNDER MELBOURNE 2024
To love them we wait
Stronger it makes us as we fight every fade
Strength to finally defeat, this journey a thousand years to meet
Yo, everybody! What's up?
We are from hololive!
Are you ready to go on a journey? Let's get started!
Sun is down, and gently we lie
Penny we still grounded by time
petty, we're still grounded by time.
A longest hops, connect your dots
Hear the echoes of aging go by
Made a splash, but found I'm not free
A fish out of water, bounds of the sea
Got a reckless high time, right here right by my side
I bet this moment's a wave we can ride
Connecting songs across the sky
Take off so high, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fade
Strength to finally defeat, this journey a thousand years to meet
Witness the fire, our minds burning inside
Rising again from the ashes
Every bruise and every scratch just makes us feel more alive
We never give up, never give in, no matter what's ahead
There's no world for us to touch or to see
We'll make it ourselves, then make memories
Connecting songs across the sky
Take off so high, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fade
Strength to finally defeat, this journey a thousand years to meet
At the end of this world, where's our fighting chance?
Nothing's changing...
It's always the same story, staged with a different dance
Got a happy end for me and my friends, and those who loved us up till now
I wanna see your smile...
Somehow, take off and slide, the longer we wait
The stronger it makes us as we fight every fade
Strength to finally defeat, this journey a thousand years to meet
Let's try, it can't be denied, the wish in my heart is
You right here by my side
Strength is all that we'll need, our one way to sound a thousand years to meet
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」っぽない
Spoiler for love: "break up"-ish
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」っぽない
Spoiler for life: "death"-ish
なにそれ意味深くて かっこいいじゃん...
What the? That's so meaningful and cool...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ 失敬
I'm dancing with a word book like that. So long.
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる 風
Tu tulu tu tu tulu-ish
神っぽいな
God-ish
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That's enough, that's enough.
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたなあい
That's enough, that's enough. I'm getting excited on the contrary.
おっきいね おっきいね 夢
It's big, it's big, your dream.
おっきいね おっきいね
It's big, it's big.
景気いいけど 品性はTHE END
The economy's good, but quality's the end.
うええい うええい
Yay, yay
“Gott ist tot”
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
That's god-ish, unfair.
神っぽいな それ "My God"
That's god-ish, "My God".
アイウオンチュー ウォンチュー IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you. Feels like my IQ's dropping.
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
That's wicked-hearted, after all.
邪心っぽいな それ "My God"
That's wicked-hearted, "My God".
アイヘイチュー ヘイチュー 害虫はどっちん
I hate you, hate you. Which one of us is the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hair style, those eyes, those lips.
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that make-up.
アレっぽいな それ 比況
They're that-ish, compare.
アレっぽいな それ
They're that-ish.
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge? いきますよ～！
"Doki-doki-shite rouge? Let's go!"
孤独から生み落とされた 純真な神の子
Born from solitude, a pure child of God.
壊れないように大切に育てましょう
Let's nurture them carefully so they won't break.
私はいつでも此処で歌っているわ
I am always singing right here.
あなたがが笑いかければ 笑うでしょう きっと
If you smile at me, you'll surely smile back.
オ喰ベナサイ モット
Eat up more,
甘美ナ青リンゴ
sweet blue apple,
臓物ト結バレ
bound with entrails,
イツマデモ
forevermore.
オ喰ベナサイ モット
Eat up more,
コノ歌声ヲ
this singing voice,
知ラヌ仏トハ
to an ignorant Buddha,
トッテモ素敵ナ言葉ダコト!
what a lovely phrase!
愛して矜持して満たしなさい
Cherish, take pride, and be fulfilled,
自由に好きなように
freely, however you like,
ワタシが何度でも何度でも
No matter how many times,
許してあげるわ
I will forgive you.
あなたは何も悪くない そうでしょう? そうでしょう?
You didn't do anything wrong, right? Right?
罪とは知らず 重ね重ね
Unknowing of sin, piling it on and on,
素晴らしいわ! 愚かで!
how wonderful! How foolish!
切り取って 貼り付けては
Cut out, paste on,
都合良く塗りたくって
conveniently painting over it,
終わりなき渇きに
to an endless thirst
踊られ 夜は更けて
being danced, the night deepens,
愛と憎しみは紙一重
Love and hatred are two sides of the same coin,
理想郷からはみ出すなら
if you step out of utopia,
裏切り者と罵るだけ
they'll just curse you as a traitor.
指先で一網打尽
Wiping them out in one sweep with your fingertips.
狂イナサイ モット
Go crazy, more,
夢カ現カ
dream or reality,
曖昧ニナッテハ
becoming ambiguous,
朽チテイク
decaying away.
狂イナサイ モット
Go crazy, more,
妄想ニ溺ッテ
drowning in delusions,
片手間ノ呪文デ
with a casual spell,
今日ハ誰ヲ屠ルノカシラ?
who will you slaughter today?
さようなら 永遠に 気付かないフリ
Goodbye forever, pretending not to notice
奪われたものは どれほど?
how much was taken away?
さようなら 永遠に 言い訳は得意
Goodbye forever, excuses are my specialty,
嘆息、なんて嘆かわしい...
a sigh, how deplorable...
ソーナアナタガ大好キナノ!
That's how much I love you!
愛して矜持して満たしなさい
Cherish, take pride, and be fulfilled,
自由に好きなように
freely, however you like,
だってワタシはもうとっくに
because I am already long
私ではないのだから!
not myself anymore!
鏡をよく見てごらん なさい
Look closely into the mirror,
あなたは今まで
up until now,
誰を見て誰を愛してた?
who were you looking at, who were you loving?
愚かなその姿で
with that foolish figure of yours.
SUPA!
MEGA!
HAIPA!
SISTA!
超カワイイ！ 超ヤバイ！
CHO KAWAII! CHO YABAI!
クレイジークレイジークレイジークレイジー！
KREIJI KREIJI KREIJI KREIJI!
SUPA!
MEGA!
HAIPA!
SISTA!
超カワイイ！ 超ヤバイ！
CHO KAWAII! CHO YABAI!
オリオリオリオリ！
O-ri o-ri o-ri o-ri!
ドリドリドリナイト ドレスコードなんてないの!?
Dori-dori-dori night, aren't there any dress codes!?
きっと見劣りなんて捨ててくよ舞台！
Throwing away any sense of looking inferior, let's hit the stage!
クレイジー・クレイジー・ダンス！心とろけようなじゃに!?
Crazy crazy dance! Heart-melting, isn't it!?
見つけたっとって正解な場所 Let's go!
The right place we found, let's go!
スパ！メガ！ハイパ！シスタ！ 超カワイイ！超ヤバイ！
SUPA! MEGA! HAIPA! SISTA! CHO KAWAII! CHO YABAI!
ドリドリドリナイト ドレスコードなんてないの!?
Dori-dori-dori night, aren't there any dress codes!?
きっと見劣りなんて捨ててくよ舞台！
Throwing away any sense of looking inferior, let's hit the stage!
クレイジー・クレイジー・ダンス！心とろけようなじゃに!?
Crazy crazy dance! Heart-melting, isn't it!?
見つけたっとって正解な場所 Let's go!
The right place we found, let's go!
ドリドリドリナイト ドレスコードなんてないの!?
Dori-dori-dori night, aren't there any dress codes!?
Let's crazy party night!
Are you ready?
Yay!
Thank you for listening!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge? いきますよ～！
"Do-ki do-ki shi-te rouge? Let's go!"
Are you ready? Yay!
無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent!
マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling, even more dizzying!
ねぇ、言ったよね？ 年齢なんて関係ないってさ そういう面倒くさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
Hey, you said it, right? Age doesn't matter, and you'd love even those troublesome things!
ねぇねぇ、言ったよね？ 言ってない？ ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hey hey, you said it, right? You didn't? Hmph, so that's how it is.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, on this ship, 'beautiful girl innocence' applies, you know?
まかせて！ 魔法で若返り 秘密の素顔はキミにだけ トクベツですよ～？
Leave it to me! Rejuvenating with magic, this secret true face is just for you—special, right?
あぁ… アタシ厄介ょ あぁ… 港なんかじゃ はしゃないわ 最近はね 宝の島にしてほしい気分 出発ー！！
Ah... I'm troublesome. Ah... Not at ports, I don't act wild much. Kind of feeling like making it Treasure Island. Set sail!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪 キミの一番目指してヨーソロ！
Cute is justice, beautiful girl innocence. Aiming for your number one, yosoro!
本当は自信ないけど 頑張っちゃう ahoy！！
Actually I'm not confident, but I'll do my best, ahoy!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu- kyu- kyurun, kyu- kyu- kyurunrun
恋する気持ち 17歳 0時になっちゃうワ オトナの時間
Feeling of love at 17 years old, turning midnight, grown-up time.
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling, even more dizzying!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge? まだ早い♡
Do-ki do-ki shi-te rouge? Still too early♡
だっ だっ ダメですか？ フリルの服装着たら
Da- da- damu desu ka? If I wear frilly clothes,
そんなこと、ないよっ だっだっだっだって
no way, such a thing—da-da-da-da-dattete
魔法少女になってみたい ギリギリー有罪！？
wanting to become a magical girl, barely guilty!?
進路はなん なん 星 ちょっと足んない積極性？
Course is wha- wha- what star? A little lacking in proactivity?
結局キミももっと若い子？ なんて言うから見捨てないでで、キミたち！
In the end, you too want an even younger girl? Saying things like that, don't abandon me, you guys!
ちょっとイイとこ見せてみィ～い！ あぁ… たまにいじけちゃう
Show me a cool side for once! Ah... sometimes I get sullen.
あぁ… それでもいいの？ 年齢だもん本気にしちゃう
Ah... Is even that okay? It's about age, so I'll take it seriously.
嵐の中も 一緒に、行こう？ 出発ー！！
Even through the storm, let's go together? Set sail!!
ハートにチャーム 美少女無罪 あれあれどーしたって
Charm on heart, beautiful girl innocence, what what, how come,
めんどくさいよなんて言っちゃって かまってくれるキミが好き ahoy！！
saying 'how troublesome', I love the you who pays attention to me, ahoy!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu- kyu- kyurun, kyu- kyu- kyurunrun
優しくしてね 17歳 突っ込んで経験知識 お楽しみ chu♡
Treat me gently, 17 years old, dive into experience and knowledge, enjoying chu♡
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge?
As expected, sparkling, even more dizzying, do-ki do-ki shi-te rouge?
あぁ、お許しくだ～い！ このマリンの……
Ah, please forgive me! This Marine's...
魅力！ 魔力！ 不抗争力！ ── “罪な女” ね？
Charm! Magic! Irresistible force! -- A 'sinful woman', huh?
離さないでつかまえていて 世界の広さ見せてあげるから！ 出発ー！！
Don't let go, hold onto me, I'll show you how vast the world is! Set sail!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪 キミの一番目指してヨーソロ！
Cute is justice, beautiful girl innocence. Aiming for your number one, yosoro!
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ ahoy！！
I love jokes too, but I'm dead serious, ahoy!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu- kyu- kyurun, kyu- kyu- kyurunrun
恋する気持ち 17歳 0時になっちゃうワ オトナの時間
Feeling of love at 17 years old, turning 0 o'clock, grown-up time.
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge? まだ早い♡
As expected, sparkling, even more dizzying, do-ki do-ki shi-te rouge? Still too early♡
無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！ マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent! Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling, even more dizzying,
“マリン”じゃなくて “マリン船長”だろうん！？
not 'Marine', but 'Captain Marine', right!?
仲間も
Even companions...
宇宙噛み砕き
crushing through the cosmos,
船長！
Captain!
Sexy世界一superピチピチ ぶっちょけ船長捕まえたい？
The world's sexiest, super fresh captain—wanna catch her?
you're gonna get the treasure
maybe tasting me
私の甘さが欲しいでしょ
Want a taste of my sweetness?
じれったい貴方の手
Your impatient hands,
海図にこぼす甘いため息tease
spilling sweet sighs of tease across the sea chart.
純紅のバラがしおれる前に
Before the crimson roses wither,
we will sail the seven seas
キュッキュッキュるんキュッキュッキュるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, kyu-kyu-kyurun,
優しくしてねチューぶなでで
treat me gently.
突っ込んでけ異見地 お楽しみ中
Dive into opinions, enjoying ourselves.
ドキドキしてる
My heart is racing,
お許しくだちゃい
please forgive me.
この胸の魅力 魔力 深層効力
The charm, magic, and deep effect of this chest...
罪な女ね
Such a sinful woman.
離さないで 捕まえていて
Don't let go, hold on tight.
世界のどこだって見せてあげるから
I'll show you anywhere in the world.
キュッキュッキュるんキュッキュッキュるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, kyu-kyu-kyurun.
君の一番目指してよっとろ
Aiming for your number one.
冗談も大好きだけど 神経よ
I love jokes too, but be serious.
キュッキュッキュるんキュッキュッキュるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, kyu-kyu-kyurun.
恋する気持ち 宙舞え
Feelings of love dance through the air.
てっぺんに来ちゃったわ 大人の時間
We've reached the top, adult time.
ドキドキしてる
My heart is racing,
まだ早い
it's still too early.
うるさい うるさい うるさい まりおん まりうん まりうむ うるさい
So noisy, noisy, noisy!
ヤッパキラキラ マックラクラ アホイ！
Still sparkly, pitch dark, ahoy!
Captain of the treasure forest 宝箱開けちゃって
Captain of the treasure forest, open up that chest!
How are you guys feeling?!
You doing good?
I'm speechless!
ちょっと待って、マイクが...どこ？どこ？
Wait a second, my mic... where is it?
Well, while she's figuring that out, should we do an introduction?
見つけた！ I can speak again! あ、she's here!
Found it! I can speak again! Ah, she's here!
I'm alive, which is ironic.
Hey everybody, what's up?!
I guess we should do an introduction.
Yeah, you can go first.
I guess because I am senpai, here I go.
みなさん！ it's me, Mori Calliope from Hololive English.
Everyone! It's me, Mori Calliope from Hololive English!
English hardworking shinigami, reaper, rapper, singer, nice to meet you!
Hardworking shinigami, reaper, rapper, singer!
Who is that? Who am I? What's up?!
I am Kobo Kanaeru, the end of men. Your local Aussie rep has come home!
I am Kobo Kanaeru, the shaman. Your local Aussie rep has come home!
And we'll take some Hololive English, witness me!
Witness! Witness me!
Alright, so some of you may already know, I think a lot of you already know of us...
Alright, so some of you may already know of us...
...but I'm going to tell you a little bit about VTubers for those that don't know.
...but I'm going to tell you a little bit about VTubers.
So, let me clear something up. Not AI!
We're not AI!
No, no, no. We are many things.
We are singers, dancers, performers, a lot of us are gamers...
We are singers, dancers, performers, gamers...
...I know some of you guys are gamers. Gamer here, gamer there! I see them everywhere.
...I know some of you guys are gamers. Gamer here, gamer there!
But, but the main thing is we are real! And we just look like this.
But the main thing is we are real! And we just look like this.
We are real people, and we just look like this. That's the only difference, right?
We are real people, and we just look like this. That's the difference, right?
And we belong to Hololive Production! Anyone know Hololive Production?
And we belong to Hololive Production! Anyone know them?
Hololive Production is a virtual idol agency that is based in Japan, but we are also reaching overseas! We want to become worldwide!
Hololive Production is a virtual idol agency based in Japan, but reaching overseas!
I have a question though. Yes. Are you guys having a good time so far?!
I have a question. Are you guys having a good time so far?!
And how about you guys watching on the stream? We see you!
We see you! We see you! ありがとうございまーす！
We see you! Thank you very much!
Thank you! We made it! We're Melbourne!
It's a real place!
Are you sure?
Are you sure it's Melbourne?
We're in Melbourne!
But they fly us somewhere else, like maybe a different, like a like some place like like off of like America.
But they fly us somewhere else... Like maybe somewhere like off in America?
No, it's real!
It's real!
We're real, they're real.
They just take us to London or something like that.
Can you say Melbourne?
Was that Can you say Melbourne?
Melbourne.
Melbourne. Melbourne.
What?
Is there something wrong with the way I said Melbourne?
Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne.
Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne. Melbourne.
Melbourne, what what's wrong? You have to tell
Melbourne, what's wrong? You have to tell me.
You got to give me something, babe. You got to give me something.
You gotta give me something, babe. You gotta give me something.
What am I saying?
Uh, you're doing it perfectly, right guys?
It's Melbourne. It's Melbourne. It's Melbourne. It's Melbourne.
It's Melbourne! It's Melbourne!
Melbourne. Melbourne.
Ben. Am I saying it better now?
No, Mel bin. Mel bin. Mel bin. Yeah, it's close enough.
No, Mel-bin. Mel-bin. Yeah, it's close enough.
All right.
But, yeah, we've arrived in Melbourne and we're so excited to be here.
That's right, there's a lot of stuff here actually, right?
Yeah, there is. There's like art all over the place
and like really good food. Yeah, the chicken is so good.
and like really good food. Yeah, the chicken's so good!
The chicken is like the chicken.
Um, yeah, so Melbourne is known for a lot of things, but if you know me, obviously caffeine is my jam.
For those who are  new to Melbourne, I highly encourage you to check out all the coffee shops cuz the coffee is the best in Melbourne!
For those who are new to Melbourne, I highly encourage you to check out all the coffee shops, 'cause the coffee is the best in Melbourne!
Woo! \u200b So, yeah, please do check out Melbourne if you guys have the chance. There's a lot of cool things, a lot of museums, galleries, and plenty of fun experiences for you to try!
Woo! So, yeah, please do check out Melbourne if you guys have the chance. There's a lot of cool things, a lot of museums, galleries, and plenty of fun experiences for you to try!
That's right. Also, speaking of loving chicken, hey, you and the crowd who did like the Takamori like art
That's right. Also, speaking of loving chicken, hey, you and the crowd who did like the Takamori art
and me and PR like kissing thing, you're not going to get away with that. I'm just letting you know tonight.
and me and Kiara kissing... You're not going to get away with that. I'm just letting you know.
Good job. Good job. Good job. Hey, don't encourage them.
Good job. Good job. Hey, don't encourage them!
Anyway, we do have a bit of sad news.
Yes, we do have sad news for you guys, um the sneak peek part of the show is unfortunately ending here.
But for those on stream who want to \u200b see more, please buy the ticket at Spawn on this one. If you guys if you guys want to keep watching, \u200b um \u200b Oh, for you guys at the venue don't worry about it. \u200b
But for those on stream who want to see more, please buy the ticket at SpawN for this one. If you guys want to keep watching... Oh, for you guys at the venue, don't worry about it.
Yeah, you guys don't have to do anything else. Just sit there and have fun, \u200b okay?
Yeah, you guys don't have to do anything else. Just sit there and have fun, okay?
Yeah. \u200b And \u200b so as for everybody else that's going to come along with us, \u200b let's \u200b keep it \u200b going!
Yeah! And so, as for everybody else that's going to come along with us, let's keep it going!
Yay! Yay! \u200b Yeah! \u200b Woo!
Yay! Yeah! Woo!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!